{
    "subject": "Guan_Hu",
    "predicate": "directed",
    "object": "Dirt__1994_film_",
    "human_readable": "Guan Hu directed the film Dirt (1994).",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.7629756331443787,
            "question": "Who directed the film Dirt?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7213156819343567,
            "question": "What is the name of the film directed by Guan Hu?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6121438145637512,
            "question": "Is Guan Hu a filmmaker?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5470165610313416,
            "question": "What year was the film Dirt released?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4939693212509155,
            "question": "Can you name another film directed by Guan Hu?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.37459343671798706,
            "question": "What are some other films from 1994?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3128884434700012,
            "question": "What genre is the film Dirt likely to be?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2803795635700226,
            "question": "What might be a common theme explored in a film titled 'Dirt'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.24693083763122559,
            "question": "Would you recommend watching the film Dirt?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.22172680497169495,
            "question": "Where do you think the film Dirt was set?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Guan Hu directed the film Dirt (1994).",
            "html": "yago_17269_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Would you recommend watching the film Dirt?",
            "html": "yago_17269_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What might be a common theme explored in a film titled 'Dirt'?",
            "html": "yago_17269_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What genre is the film Dirt likely to be?",
            "html": "yago_17269_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_17269_151.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_17269_36.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_17269_40.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_17269_41.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_17269_65.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_17269_66.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_17269_73.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_17269_78.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_17269_85.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_17269_88.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the answer in JSON format:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information in the documents supports this triple, as it is mentioned that \"Dirt\" is a Chinese film from 1994 which depicts the nascent rock music scene of Beijing, and Guan Hu directed the film."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information about the director Guan Hu and his film \"Dirt\" from 1994, confirming that he directed it."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n    \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "mistral-nemo": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "-",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}